Senate fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Senate Committees, 1965 - 1987; F-84-1; 13.72 m of textual records
  - Senate Committee on Graduate Studies (SCGS), 1966 - 1986; F-84-1-9; 4.82 m of textual records
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. - May 1969, F-84-1-9-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-62)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. June - July 1969, F-84-1-9-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-62)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. - Oct. 1969, F-84-1-9-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-62)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 1969, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-63)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 1969, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-63)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1969, F-84-1-9-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-63)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. - Feb. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-63)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-63)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-63)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. - Apr. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-63)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 1970, F-84-1-9-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-64)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. June 1970, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-64)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. June 1971, vol. 2, 1970; F-84-1-9-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-64)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. June 1972, vol. 3, 1970; F-84-1-9-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-64)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. June - July 1970, F-84-1-9-0-20 (Archival box - standard 84-64)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July - Aug. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-21 (Archival box - standard 84-64)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-22 (Archival box - standard 84-65)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. - Nov. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-23 (Archival box - standard 84-65)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-24 (Archival box - standard 84-65)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. - Dec. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-25 (Archival box - standard 84-65)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1970, F-84-1-9-0-26 (Archival box - standard 84-65)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. - Mar. 1971, F-84-1-9-0-27 (Archival box - standard 84-65)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. - Apr. 1971, F-84-1-9-0-28 (Archival box - standard 84-65)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1971, F-84-1-9-0-29 (Archival box - standard 84-66)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May - June 1971, F-84-1-9-0-30 (Archival box - standard 84-66)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 1971, F-84-1-9-0-31 (Archival box - standard 84-66)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July 1971, F-84-1-9-0-32 (Archival box - standard 84-66)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Aug. 1971, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-33 (Archival box - standard 84-66)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Aug. 1971, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-34 (Archival box - standard 84-66)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. - Oct. 1971, F-84-1-9-0-35 (Archival box - standard 84-66)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. - Nov. 1971, F-84-1-9-0-36 (Archival box - standard 84-67)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. -Dec. 1971, F-84-1-9-0-37 (Archival box - standard 84-67)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1971, F-84-1-9-0-38 (Archival box - standard 84-67)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. - Feb. 1972, F-84-1-9-0-39 (Archival box - standard 84-67)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Mar. 1972, F-84-1-9-0-40 (Archival box - standard 84-67)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1972, F-84-1-9-0-41 (Archival box - standard 84-68)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1972, F-84-1-9-0-42 (Archival box - standard 84-68)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 1972, F-84-1-9-0-43 (Archival box - standard 84-68)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 1972, F-84-1-9-0-44 (Archival box - standard 84-68)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. July 1972, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-45 (Archival box - standard 84-68)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. July 1973, vol. 2, 1972; F-84-1-9-0-46 (Archival box - standard 84-68)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. July 1974, vol. 3, 1972; F-84-1-9-0-47 (Archival box - standard 84-68)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Aug. 1972, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-48 (Archival box - standard 84-69)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Aug. 1972, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-49 (Archival box - standard 84-69)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 1972, F-84-1-9-0-50 (Archival box - standard 84-69)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. - Oct. 1972, F-84-1-9-0-51 (Archival box - standard 84-69)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1972, F-84-1-9-0-52 (Archival box - standard 84-69)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. - Dec. 1972, F-84-1-9-0-53 (Archival box - standard 84-69)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Dec. 1972, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-54 (Archival box - standard 84-70)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Dec. 1972, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-55 (Archival box - standard 84-70)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 1973, F-84-1-9-0-56 (Archival box - standard 84-70)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Feb. 1973, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-57 (Archival box - standard 84-70)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Feb. 1973, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-58 (Archival box - standard 84-70)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Mar. 1973, F-84-1-9-0-59 (Archival box - standard 84-70)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Apr. 1973, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-60 (Archival box - standard 84-70)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 1973, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-61 (Archival box - standard 84-71)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Apr. 1973, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-62 (Archival box - standard 84-71)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. - May 1973, F-84-1-9-0-63 (Archival box - standard 84-71)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May - June 1973, F-84-1-9-0-64 (Archival box - standard 84-71)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. July 1973, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-65 (Archival box - standard 84-71)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. July 1974, vol. 2, 1973; F-84-1-9-0-66 (Archival box - standard 84-71)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Aug. 1973, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-67 (Archival box - standard 84-72)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Aug. 1973, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-68 (Archival box - standard 84-72)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Aug. 1973, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-69 (Archival box - standard 84-72)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 1973, F-84-1-9-0-70 (Archival box - standard 84-72)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1973, F-84-1-9-0-71 (Archival box - standard 84-72)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 1973, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-72 (Archival box - standard 84-72)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 1973, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-73 (Archival box - standard 84-72)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Dec. 1973, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-74 (Archival box - standard 84-73)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Dec. 1973, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-75 (Archival box - standard 84-73)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 1974, F-84-1-9-0-76 (Archival box - standard 84-73)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. - Feb. 1974, F-84-1-9-0-77 (Archival box - standard 84-73)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. -Apr. 1974, F-84-1-9-0-78 (Archival box - standard 84-73)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Apr. 1974, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-79 (Archival box - standard 84-73)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 1974, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-80 (Archival box - standard 84-74)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Apr. 1974, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-81 (Archival box - standard 84-74)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 4. Apr. 1974, vol. 4, F-84-1-9-0-82 (Archival box - standard 84-74)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 5. Apr. 1974, vol. 5, F-84-1-9-0-83 (Archival box - standard 84-74)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. June 1974, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-84 (Archival box - standard 84-74)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. June 1975, vol. 2, 1974; F-84-1-9-0-85 (Archival box - standard 84-74)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. July 1974, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-86 (Archival box - standard 84-75)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. July 1975, vol. 2, 1974; F-84-1-9-0-87 (Archival box - standard 84-75)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. July 1976, vol. 3, 1974; F-84-1-9-0-88 (Archival box - standard 84-75)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Aug. 1974, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-89 (Archival box - standard 84-75)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Aug. 1974, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-90 (Archival box - standard 84-75)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. - Oct. 1974, F-84-1-9-0-91 (Archival box - standard 84-75)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. - Nov. 1974, F-84-1-9-0-92 (Archival box - standard 84-76)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 1974, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-93 (Archival box - standard 84-76)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 1974, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-94 (Archival box - standard 84-76)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Dec. 1974, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-95 (Archival box - standard 84-76)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Dec. 1974, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-96 (Archival box - standard 84-76)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. - Feb. 1975, F-84-1-9-0-97 (Archival box - standard 84-76)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 1975, F-84-1-9-0-98 (Archival box - standard 84-76)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 1975, F-84-1-9-0-99 (Archival box - standard 84-77)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Apr. 1975, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-100 (Archival box - standard 84-77)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 1975, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-101 (Archival box - standard 84-77)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Apr. 1975, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-102 (Archival box - standard 84-77)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 1975, F-84-1-9-0-103 (Archival box - standard 84-77)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May - June 1975, F-84-1-9-0-104 (Archival box - standard 84-77)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. June 1975, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-105 (Archival box - standard 84-78)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. June 1975, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-106 (Archival box - standard 84-78)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July 1975, F-84-1-9-0-107 (Archival box - standard 84-78)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Aug. 1975, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-108 (Archival box - standard 84-78)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Aug. 1975, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-109 (Archival box - standard 84-78)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 1975, F-84-1-9-0-110 (Archival box - standard 84-79)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Oct. 1975, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-111 (Archival box - standard 84-79)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 1975, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-112 (Archival box - standard 84-79)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Nov. 1975, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-113 (Archival box - standard 84-79)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 4. Nov. 1975, vol. 4, F-84-1-9-0-114 (Archival box - standard 84-79)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1975, F-84-1-9-0-115 (Archival box - standard 84-79)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Dec. 1975, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-116 (Archival box - standard 84-79)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Dec. 1975, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-117 (Archival box - standard 84-80)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Dec. 1975, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-118 (Archival box - standard 84-80)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 4. Dec. 1975, vol. 4, F-84-1-9-0-119 (Archival box - standard 84-80)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. - Feb. 1976, F-84-1-9-0-120 (Archival box - standard 84-80)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Mar. 1976, F-84-1-9-0-121 (Archival box - standard 84-80)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 1976, F-84-1-9-0-122 (Archival box - standard 84-80)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. - Apr. 1976, F-84-1-9-0-123 (Archival box - standard 84-81)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Apr. 1976, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-124 (Archival box - standard 84-81)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 1976, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-125 (Archival box - standard 84-81)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Apr. 1976, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-126 (Archival box - standard 84-81)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. May 1976, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-127 (Archival box - standard 84-81)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. May 1976, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-128 (Archival box - standard 84-81)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 1976, F-84-1-9-0-129 (Archival box - standard 84-81)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. July 1976, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-130 (Archival box - standard 84-82)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. July 1976, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-131 (Archival box - standard 84-82)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Aug. 1976, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-132 (Archival box - standard 84-82)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Aug. 1976, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-133 (Archival box - standard 84-82)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 1976, F-84-1-9-0-134 (Archival box - standard 84-82)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1976, F-84-1-9-0-135 (Archival box - standard 84-82)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. - Nov. 1976, F-84-1-9-0-136 (Archival box - standard 84-82)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1976, F-84-1-9-0-137 (Archival box - standard 84-82)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Dec. 1976, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-138 (Archival box - standard 84-83)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Dec. 1976, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-139 (Archival box - standard 84-83)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Dec. 1976, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-140 (Archival box - standard 84-83)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 1977, F-84-1-9-0-141 (Archival box - standard 84-83)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 1977, F-84-1-9-0-142 (Archival box - standard 84-83)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - Apr. 1977, F-84-1-9-0-143 (Archival box - standard 84-83)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Apr. 1977, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-144 (Archival box - standard 84-84)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 1977, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-145 (Archival box - standard 84-84)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Apr. 1977, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-146 (Archival box - standard 84-84)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 1977, F-84-1-9-0-147 (Archival box - standard 84-84)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 1977, F-84-1-9-0-148 (Archival box - standard 84-84)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July1977, F-84-1-9-0-149 (Archival box - standard 84-84)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Aug. 1977, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-150 (Archival box - standard 84-84)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Aug. 1977, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-151 (Archival box - standard 84-85)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Aug. 1977, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-152 (Archival box - standard 84-85)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 1977, F-84-1-9-0-153 (Archival box - standard 84-85)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. - Nov. 1977, F-84-1-9-0-154 (Archival box - standard 84-85)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1977, F-84-1-9-0-155 (Archival box - standard 84-85)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. - Dec. 1977, F-84-1-9-0-156 (Archival box - standard 84-85)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1977, F-84-1-9-0-157 (Archival box - standard 84-85)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. -Feb. 1978, F-84-1-9-0-158 (Archival box - standard 84-86)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Apr. 1978, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-159 (Archival box - standard 84-86)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 1978, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-160 (Archival box - standard 84-86)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Apr. 1978, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-161 (Archival box - standard 84-86)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May - June 1978, F-84-1-9-0-162 (Archival box - standard 84-86)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July 1978, F-84-1-9-0-163 (Archival box - standard 84-86)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. 1978, F-84-1-9-0-164 (Archival box - standard 84-87)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Sept. 1978, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-165 (Archival box - standard 84-87)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Sept. 1978, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-166 (Archival box - standard 84-87)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. - Nov. 1978, F-84-1-9-0-167 (Archival box - standard 84-87)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. - Dec. 1978, F-84-1-9-0-168 (Archival box - standard 84-87)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. - Apr. 1979, F-84-1-9-0-169 (Archival box - standard 84-87)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Apr. 1979, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-170 (Archival box - standard 84-87)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 1979, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-171 (Archival box - standard 84-87)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May - June 1979, F-84-1-9-0-172 (Archival box - standard 84-88)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July - Sept. 1979, F-84-1-9-0-173 (Archival box - standard 84-88)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Sept. 1979, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-174 (Archival box - standard 84-88)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Sept. 1979, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-175 (Archival box - standard 84-88)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Sept. 1979, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-176 (Archival box - standard 84-88)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1979, F-84-1-9-0-178 (Archival box - standard 84-88)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. - Dec. 1979, F-84-1-9-0-179 (Archival box - standard 84-88)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 1980, F-84-1-9-0-180 (Archival box - standard 84-88)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 1980, F-84-1-9-0-181 (Archival box - standard 84-88)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Mar. 1980, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-182 (Archival box - standard 84-89)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Mar. 1980, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-183 (Archival box - standard 84-89)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Mar. 1980, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-184 (Archival box - standard 84-89)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 4. Mar. 1980, vol. 4, F-84-1-9-0-185 (Archival box - standard 84-89)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1980, F-84-1-9-0-186 (Archival box - standard 84-89)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. June - July 1980, F-84-1-9-0-187 (Archival box - standard 84-89)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July - Aug. 1980, F-84-1-9-0-188 (Archival box - standard 84-89)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Sept. 1980, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-189 (Archival box - standard 84-89)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Sept. 1980, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-190 (Archival box - standard 84-89)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Sept. 1980, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-191 (Archival box - standard 84-90)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. - Dec. 1980, F-84-1-9-0-192 (Archival box - standard 84-90)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Dec. 1980, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-193 (Archival box - standard 84-90)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Dec. 1980, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-194 (Archival box - standard 84-90)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Dec. 1980, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-195 (Archival box - standard 84-90)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 4. Dec. 1980, vol. 4, F-84-1-9-0-196 (Archival box - standard 84-90)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1980 - Feb. 1981, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-9-0-197 (Archival box - standard 84-90)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Apr. 1981, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-198 (Archival box - standard 84-90)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Apr. 1981, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-199 (Archival box - standard 84-90)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Apr. 1981, vol. 3, F-84-1-9-0-200 (Archival box - standard 84-91)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. - June 1981, F-84-1-9-0-201 (Archival box - standard 84-91)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. July - Aug. 1981, F-84-1-9-0-202 (Archival box - standard 84-91)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. - Oct. 1981, F-84-1-9-0-203 (Archival box - standard 84-91)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1981, F-84-1-9-0-204 (Archival box - standard 84-91)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 1982, F-84-1-9-0-205 (Archival box - standard 84-91)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 1982, F-84-1-9-0-206 (Archival box - standard 84-92)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 1982, F-84-1-9-0-207 (Archival box - standard 84-92)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. May 1982, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-208 (Archival box - standard 84-92)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. May 1982, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-209 (Archival box - standard 84-92)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May - July 1982, F-84-1-9-0-210 (Archival box - standard 84-92)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Sept. 1982, vol. 1, F-84-1-9-0-211 (Archival box - standard 84-92)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Sept. 1982, vol. 2, F-84-1-9-0-212 (Archival box - standard 84-92)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. - Nov. 1982, F-84-1-9-0-213 (Archival box - standard 84-93)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 1982, F-84-1-9-0-214 (Archival box - standard 84-93)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1982, F-84-1-9-0-215 (Archival box - standard 84-93)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1982, F-84-1-9-0-216 (Archival box - standard 84-93)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1982, F-84-1-9-0-217 (Archival box - standard 84-93)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 1983, F-84-1-9-0-218 (Archival box - standard 84-93)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 1983, F-84-1-9-0-219 (Archival box - standard 84-94)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 1983, F-84-1-9-0-220 (Archival box - standard 84-94)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 1983, F-84-1-9-0-221 (Archival box - standard 84-94)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 1983, F-84-1-9-0-222 (Archival box - standard 84-94)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 1983, F-84-1-9-0-223 (Archival box - standard 84-94)